marketing.us 2004-06-23

# Pay Per Click Search Engine PPC Search Engine Cost Per Click

|  Privacy Policy

Your privacy is extremely important to us. Following is our policy regarding how we protect the privacy of the personal information you provide us. SearchEngine.us collects information when you register with SearchEngine.us. When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, zip code, your address. SearchEngine.us automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, SearchEngine.us cookie information and another accessible information.

SearchEngine.us uses information for the following general purposes: improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

SearchEngine.us does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except under the following circumstances: -We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with SearchEngine.us under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your information to help SearchEngine.us communicate with you about offers from SearchEngine.us and our marketing partners. -We respond to court orders or legal process.

SearchEngine.us does not provide any individually identifiable information to the advertiser.  
  
---  
   
Cookies

SearchEngine.us may set and access SearchEngine.us cookies on your computer. SearchEngine.us lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages and/or network to set and access their cookies on your computer.  

Surveys

From time to time, we or a company selected by us may offer you the opportunity to participate in surveys. You may be asked to provide membership information to participate. All surveys are optional.  

Contests

We may from time to time offer you the opportunity to participate in sweepstakes, product giveaways and similar services. You will be asked to provide membership information to participate in any sweepstakes or giveaways. We or a company selected by us administers the sweepstakes and contacts the winner. All sweepstakes are optional.  

Advertising

We use our own advertising as well as third party advertising agencies. We cannot be held responsible for anything contained within our partners, our members, or our advertisers sites.  

Permission To Use Your Content

By transmitting any suggestions, information, identification, material, or other content ("content") to us, you automatically grant us the royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable, non-exclusive right and license to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate, create derivative works from, distribute, redistribute, transmit, perform and display such content (in whole or part) worldwide and/or to incorporate it in other works in any form, media, or technology now known or later developed for the full term of any rights that may exist in such content. Further, we are free to use any ideas, concepts, know-how, techniques, and suggestions contained in any communications you send to this Site for any purpose whatsoever, including but not limited to creating, manufacturing, and marketing products and/or services using such information.  

General

You can edit your SearchEngine.us Account Information at any time. Communications from SearchEngine.us, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the SearchEngine.us Newsletter, are considered part of SearchEngine.us membership and you may not opt out of receiving them. We limit access to information about you to employees who need to come into contact with that information to provide services to you or in order to do their jobs. Your SearchEngine.us Account Information is password-protected.  

Changes to this Privacy Policy

SearchEngine.us may update Privacy Policy from time to time without notice to you. Please check these Privacy Policy periodically for changes. By using SearchEngine.us web site after changes have been made to Privacy Policy, you agree to the changes.
